question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Books",
        "question": "'Elementary, my dear Watson' is a phrase that is never truly said within the Conan Doyle books of Sherlock Holmes.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "The anime 'Lucky Star' follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of 'Doomhammer'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles",
     "question": "The term 'GTO' was originated by Ferrari?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In career mode of 'Need for Speed: Underground 2', the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}

]
